Amitabh Raj

Back-end Developer

amitabhraj07@gmail.com

Patna, Bihar, India 🗣

(+91 8409913276) 📞

www.linkedin.com/in/amitabhraj/in

A high school student who does not have a college degree but well Experienced in the field of Programing and with proven end-to-end development skills. Worked in Two Startup Companies as Full stack web Developer and made Company Profitable and raise the Efficiency of The Company.

Education

Grade 10th

Millennium World School, Patna

2021-2022

Work Experience

Django Backend Developer Intern at BPSC

i had done an internship in a Start-up Company as a django backend Developer where i have integrated some Features like payment Gateway,Google Login Feature and many more...and also Deployed that website using Amazon ec2 instance

june, 2021- April, 2022

Full Stack Web Developer Intern at Sarva Suvidhaen

Currently i am doing an internship in a Solar Panel Based Start-up Company as a Full Stack web Developer where i am Making a real time Data Graph using IOT and i will be Deploying this website using Amazon ec2 instance as well.

june, 2021 - Currently Working

Personal Achievement

- Made E-commerce Website using Django and Deployed on Pythonanywhere
- Made BMI Index Website using Flask and Deployed on Pythonanywhere
- Participated in a Al Workshop Organised by Guvi

Technical Skills

- Git/Github
- Linux (Intermediate)
- AWS (beginner)

Personal Skills

- Reliable
- Collabrative
- Enthusiast
- Management

Programming Skills

- python ★★★★★
- HTML/CSS ★★★★☆
- Javascript ★★★☆☆

Certification/Courses

- Certification in Django From Google
- Certification in python on Guvi
- Certification in Git and Github From Google

Library/Framework

- Django ★★★★★
- Flask ★★★★☆
- BootStrap ★★★★☆
- React.js ★★★☆☆
- Node.js ★★★☆☆